# JOSHUA ANTHONY A. DELGADO

# **Web Developer**

+639103403757

O Brgy. Ibabang Dupay, Lucena City, Philippines

joshuadelgado073@gmail.com
dev-jdelgado.github.io/web-portfolio/

### **SUMMARY**

A web developer proficient in web development mainly HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind, React.js, Vue.js, and WordPress. In addition to technical skills, also proficient in some editing tools like Photoshop, Figma, and Canva, as well as git controls and GitHub. Brings web design concepts into a working and functional website and develops and maintains user-facing features for web applications, ensures optimal performance across platforms, and optimizes user experience on mobile and desktop.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Front-End Web Developer | Floor23 Digital LTD

Feb 2024 - Present

- Developed user-facing features for web applications aimed at innovation competitions and digital marketing campaigns.
- Ensures optimal performance and responsiveness across platforms, focusing on mobile and desktop compatibility.
- Collaborates with back-end developers and designers to ensure seamless integration and high-quality outputs.

# Clerk/Encoder | Southern Luzon State University

Feb 2023 - Sept 2024

- Encode/Scans permanent records/documents to the Records Inventory System (RIS).
- Administer the Records Inventory System (RIS).
- Provide assistance with the disposal of valueless records.

### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Technical-Vocational in Teachers Education major in Computer

2018 - 2022

# Programming

Southern Luzon State University

- Major in Computer Programming.
- · Graduated with a Latin Honor
- Thesis on "Mobile-Based Tabulation System on Scholastic Competition".

# Information in Communications Technology major in Mobile App and Web

2016 - 2018

### Development

STI College Lucena

• Major in Mobile App and Web Development.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5

Bootstrap

React.js

Figma

• CSS

Tailwind

Vue.js

Canva Editor

JavaScript

WordPress

• PHP

Microsoft Offices

MySQL

GitHub

Adobe Premiere Pro

## **TRAININGS**

Knowledge Transfer of Server and UTM Training (2022)

National Certificate ii in Computer System Servicing Training (2020) Post Evaluation: DICT-SLSU Cybersecurity Awareness Webinar (2020)

# **LICENSE / CERTIFICATES**

License Professional Teacher - (LET) Passer (2023)

Certificate of Eligibility (Honor Graduate Eligibility) (2023)

National Certifi cate ii in Computer System Servicing Passer (2020)